rcrdlbl.com 2013-09-06

# PRIVACY POLICY

## PRIVACY POLICY

Please read this statement regarding our site. If you have questions please contact us at  

**Introduction**  
**Collection of data**  
**Use of data**  
**Email Addresses**  
**Ownership of Information**  
**Cookies**  
**Third Party Cookies**  
**Traffic Reports**  
**Business Transitions**  
**Links**  
**Editing or deleting your account information**  
**Other Information / Logging and Cookies**  
**Notification of Changes**  
**Contact Information**

**Introduction**

The site editor takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor's control. Please take time to read this site's Terms of Use.

**Collection of data**

Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address and a user name that has not been chosen already. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to. Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and any other information you enter may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally (depending on choices you make during the registration process, or depending on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.

**Use of data**

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy.

**Email Addresses**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third-party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don't currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our Contact Form.

**Ownership of Information**

RCRD LBL is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Cookies**

Like most web sites, we currently assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third-party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

Some of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. RCRD LBL does not have access to this data.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular. Your specific data is not shared with advertisers.

**Business Transitions**

If RCRD LBL is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

RCRD LBL regularly links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by RCRD LBL.

**Editing or deleting your account information**

You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting your user account control panel. You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact the site administrator. Content or other data that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as articles published, may continue to remain on the site at the site editor's discretion, even after your user account is deleted. Please see the site's Terms of Use for more information.

**Other Information / Logging and Cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use “persistent cookies” to save your username and login password for future logins to the Site. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of our service, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Site. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the services.

We also use the services of a third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>. 

**Notification of Changes**

When RCRD LBL makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:  

## Comments
